

CORRIN ALICIA ANAK NERO

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE WITH HONOURS (COGNITIVE SCIENCE) - UNIVERSITI MALAYSIA SARAWAK

PROFILE

Gender Female

Phone 016-889 2093

Email aliciacorrin96@gmail.com

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I would describe myself as a motivated person who thrives at learning new skills and enjoys working alongside others. My experience with various curricular activities has helped in developing my confidence and communication skills. I am also willing to take any necessary training needed to enable me to perform my tasks well.

COMPUTER SKILLS

- Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, Powerpoint, Access)
- SWI Prolog
- MySQL
- PHP
- HTML
- C++

LANGUAGE SKILLS

- · English
- Malay
- Iban

WORK EXPERIENCE

DYSLEXIA ASSOCIATION OF SARAWAK

Intern (June 2018 - August 2018)

SUGARBUN, SUMMER MALL

Cashier (June 2016 - July 2016)

TADIKA RHEMA, KUCHING

Trainee Teacher (January 2015 - February 2015)

EDUCATION BACKGROUND

Universiti Malaysia September 2016 - present Sarawak (UNIMAS)

- Bachelor of Science with Honours (Cognitive Science)
- Current CGPA: 3.50

Cognitive Science is a scientific, interdisciplinary study of the mind and its processes. It encompasses the disciplines from Psychology, Neuroscience, Linguistics, Artificial Intelligence and Philosophy, which focuses on investigating the nature of mind and intelligence.

SMK St Thomas, Kuching May 2014 - December 2015

- Sijil Tinggi Peperiksaan Malaysia (STPM)
- Science stream (Biology)
- CGPA: 2.42
- MUET Band 5

SMK St Mary, January 2009 - December 2013

- Sijil Pelajaran Malaysia (SPM)
- Pass

EXTRA CO-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

- Badan Budaya UNIMAS (BAYU) Gamelan (2017 present)
- Asas Gamelan (Credited Co-curricular, February 2017 -May 2017)
- Inter-School Christian Fellowship (SMK St Thomas, 2014 -2015)
- International Taekwondo Federation Sarawak (2005 2013)

REFERENCE

Dr. Norehan Zulkiply

- Lecturer, Faculty of Cognitive Sciences and Human Development, UNIMAS
- · Email: znorehan@unimas.my
- Office phone number: 082-584550